Chandler Tan

Salesforce Developer

(219) 381-9256 tanchandler4@gmail.com

Portfolio:

https://chandlert32.github.io/

Trailblazer Profile:

https://trailblazer.me/id/ctan4

Currently I am enrolled in the Salesforce Pathfinder Developer program with the goal of obtaining the Platform Developer I certification at the conclusion of the program on June 9, 2020. The Pathfinder program allowed me to take advantage of their structured Trailhead content, implementation case studies, and rigorous virtual technical training. I am also a recent graduate of Eleven Fifty Academy's full time Software Development program in which I learned the necessary skills to become a full-stack developer. I have experience with the languages of HTML, CSS, and the object oriented language of C#. Furthermore, I implement these languages in many of my applications. I am also very familiar with the Salesforce platform. Prior to Pathfinder and the Eleven Fifty program, I was majoring in Kinesiology and Exercise Science at Indiana State University. As of late, I have grown a passion for the creating and maintaining of certain applications. I am motivated and committed to continuing my learning to become a more contributing Salesforce Developer. Furthermore, I am more than willing to relocate to accomplish my goal.

EDUCATION

Salesforce Pathfinder Program, Indianapolis, IN - *Developer*

March 2020 - May 2020

- 55+ badges, 44,000+ points, 6 trails, Process Automation Specialist Superbadge (Expeditioner Rank)

Learned the technical and business skills necessary to pursue a career in the Salesforce ecosystem. Technical skills including experience with, fundamentals of the Salesforce platform, visualforce, lightning web components, as well as testing and debugging using Apex language. Furthermore, they provided me with all the materials needed to succeed in achieving my Platform Developer 1 certification as well as the capability of contributing in a team environment on the Salesforce platform.

Eleven Fifty Academy, Fishers, IN — *Software Development*

Jan 2020 - April 2020

In the immersive full time development program, the Academy gave me the tools to become an efficient software developer. The program covered C# and OOP fundamentals. I was also exposed to various agile methodologies. Gained experience with making Console, Web, and MVC applications. Gave me the confidence to make applications by myself, as

SKILLS

C# / HTML / CSS

Github

.NET Framework

Azure

VS Code

Salesforce Fundamentals

Developer Tools

Apex

Lightning Platform

Full-Stack experience

And more...

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Teamwork

Dependable

Problem Solver

Patient

Punctual

And more...





Indiana State University, Terre Haute, IN — Studied Kinesiology and Exercise Science

2015 - 2019

Activites: Men's soccer, intramural basketball

Merrillville High School, Merrillville, IN — Core 40

2015

Activities: Varsity Wrestling

PROJECTS - (also available on my github portfolio link...)

BlueBox — ASP.NET MVC, completed alone

Game and Movie Rental Service that utilizes .NET Framework MVC 5 Web Application using n-tier architecture. Tiers including data, models, services, and Web MVC. Allows users to rate a game/movie and rent. Implements user roles, full CRUD on multiple tables. Worked with razor syntax. Deployed to Azure.

Basic Db — database Web API, completed w/team of 4

.NET Framework API Web Application using n-tier architecture. Fictional character database that connects a character with their item (wand, sword, cloak, etc...) and type of media (movie, book, magazine, etc...). Includes custom data tables, and utilizes foreign key relationships between tables. Also implemented REST.

Hangman — console application, completed w/team of 2

Console app based around the fun game of 'Hangman'. Incorporated pair-programming. Deployed on github.

Web Store Front — HTML & CSS homepage, completed alone

'Pizza Planet' home webpage using HTML and CSS.

CSS Creature — CSS, completed alone

Created a creature on codepen using only CSS.

EXPERIENCE

Eleven Fifty Academy— .NET Development Student

Jan 2020 - April 2020

Although I was just a student here, I believed I learned the necessary skills to become a full-stack developer. EFA is where I learned the principles of

the object oriented language of C#. Along with that, I also learned how to create applications from scratch both alone and in a team. I learned many skills ranging from building storefront websites to more complex applications such as an MVC application.

Indianapolis Comic Con — *Box Office Staff*

May 2017 - May 2018

Worked at the 2017 and 2018 Indy Comic Con. Assisted customers in getting their ticket and letting them know where everything was at. Helped my bosses in moving cash boxes. Provided assistance to my fellow co-workers when needed.

JC Penny — Retail Associate

October 2016 - December 2018

Worked as a cashier as well as on the sales floor. Strived for accuracy when it came to getting work done. Assisted my boss and my peers by arranging the store and making sure everyone was doing their job correctly. Also assisted customers in whatever they needed. I was also more than welcome to accept extra tasks from my manager. Assisted in making sure various departments were properly taken care of.

Toys R Us — Retail Associate

May 2016 - August 2016

Worked as a cashier as well as on the sales floor. Assisted customers with their needs. Made sure ailes were cleaned and aligned properly. Strived for accuracy when it came to doing my job correctly.

Certifications

Salesforce Platform Developer I — *June* 9, 2020

Graduate Badge (Eleven Fifty Academy)— April 2020

The graduation badge shows that the earner successfully moved through all badges (phases) of Eleven Fifty Academy's program for the specific language/skill in which they have learned.

Credentials / More detailed info:

https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/43062e9e-d862-46fc-9d99-967ce2fb35fo/public url

Red Badge (3/3 Eleven Fifty Academy) — April 2020

Earners of .NET Red Badge take all the skills they have learned in the previous badges and work individually to create a full stack web application with .NET framework MVC and Razor. Earners work solo to plan sprints.

Credentials / More detailed info:

https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/9e3065fa-7d3f-4183-b9c2-bde631 dfc7ca/public_url

Blue Badge (2/3 Eleven Fifty Academy) — March 2020

Earners of .NET Blue Badge learn the basics of ASP.NET layered Web API development, SDLC (without maintenance), collaboration, applied problem solving, and debugging skills. Earners work in groups to plan sprints, execute daily stand ups, manage Git, intro to SOLID, and resolve issues with group dynamics.

Credentials / More detailed info:

https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/535ea75a-d853-435a-87be-45118 3fbae02/public url

Gold Badge (1/3 Eleven Fifty Academy) — February 2020

Earners of .NET Gold Badge learn fundamentals of C#, CSS, and HTML. They also learn developer tools, such as Visual Studio, Github, and Git. Earners show ability to meet deadlines and complete a series of business challenges covering C# and Object Oriented Programming fundamentals.

Credentials / More detailed info:

https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/e03e9cb2-fe02-43f5-b776-742ee63ae796/public_url